<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hr | Filippo Chiarello</title>
    <link>/tag/hr/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tag/hr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>hr</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_huce798d18068a9fdebf7468819f39f651_5224_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>hr</title>
      <link>/tag/hr/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assets&#43;</title>
      <link>/project/assets&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/assets&#43;/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved as WP1 leader. The main objective of WP1 is to  operationalize the activities coming from projects like EDSP and COSME and translate their high-level results in concrete actionable comcepts to be trained in new education and training programmes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://assets-plus.eu/results-from-wp1/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;See the results from WP1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulisse</title>
      <link>/project/external-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/external-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ULISSE project aims to unveil the true meaning of soft skills by developing the concept of “Not-So-Soft-Skills” and creating a common language with respect to soft skills among the key actors involved (intermediaries, job seekers and employers). Based on this, the project partners will design specific training paths for addressing the company’s NSSS needs, to increase the students employability and the job match-making. The training courses will be focused on tools, procedures and methods, specifically designed to address this goal, ensuring effective and Pareto efficient results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bojectives of the projects are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;identifying the companies’ real needs in the local labour market of the partner Universities (demand side)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;identifying the NSSS veiled under what we usually call “soft skills” and defining a common lexicon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;creating new training paths for answering the companies’ needs and increasing students’ employability (supply side)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;creating innovative tools for evaluating the learning impact&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;creating a toolkit to support the companies in writing more effective job offers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been mainly involved in WP1 and we developed the soft skill lexicon thank you can find &lt;a href=&#34;https://ulisseproject.eu/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Ulisseproject-Soft-skill-Lexicon.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;at this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
